<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Indicar Tuning</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1228514043878949</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb1228514043878949</string>
    <string name="kakao_app_key">be2b15c91901a83730e1cc907a1ab965</string>
    <string name="title_activity_loading">LoadingActivity</string>
    <string name="line_channel_id">1586805168</string>

    <string name="strVersionErr">The version is not correct.</string>
    <string name="strNoInternet">Your phone is not connected to the Internet. Please connect your phone to the Internet.</string>
    <string name="strLoginedErr">Failed to load user information properly. Please login again.</string>
    <string name="strAddUserSuccess">You have successfully signed up.</string>
    <string name="strCancelLogin">You have canceled your login.</string>
    <string name="strNoSearchResultErr">No results found.</string>
    <string name="strCarLoadErr">Failed to load car information. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="strNoCar">There are no cars registered yet.</string>
    <string name="strUnlink">Your account has been unsubscribed successfully. Thank you for using our services.</string>
    <string name="strUserInfoChanged">Successfully changed your information.</string>
    <string name="strErrwithCode">There is an error : </string>
    <string name="strServerCheck">The server is undergoing inspection.</string>
    <string name="strNotPrepare">This feature is in preparation. You can use it in the next update.</string>
    <string name="strNotAllowUpdateUser">The nickname can be changed after 7 days from the last change date.</string>
    <string name="strTooLongNickname">The nickname should be within 20 characters in English.</string>
    <string name="strBackpressed">Press the Back button one more time if you want to exit.</string>
    <string name="strgetUserInfoError">Failed to retrieve user information : </string>
    <string name="strPermissionDenied">You can not access the app without accepting required rights.\nYou can grant permission at [Settings] > [Permission].</string>
    <string name="strWhatPermissionDeny">Permission denied.\n</string>
    <string name="AllianceSuccess">The request for an affiliate has been successfully processed.</string>
    <string name="SignoutFail">We&apos;re sorry. An error occurred during the withdrawal processing : </string>
    <string name="SuggestSuccess">Thank you for your feedback.</string>
    <string name="lastPage">This is the last page.</string>
    <string name="reportReason">Please enter report reason.</string>
    <string name="reportSuccess">The report has been received.</string>
    <string name="wantToDelete">Are you sure you want to delete this post?</string>
    <string name="wantToDeleteSub">Once you have deleted, it can not be recovered.</string>
    <string name="deletesubtitle">Delete this post</string>
    <string name="noExistPost">This post does not exist.</string>
    <string name="commentModify">Modify Comment</string>
    <string name="commentDelete">Delete Comment</string>
    <string name="commentReport">Report inappropriate comments</string>
    <string name="deleteSlide">Are you sure you want to delete the current slide?</string>
    <string name="deleteSlideSub">Delete this slide.</string>
    <string name="deletePhoto">Are you sure you want to delete this picture?</string>
    <string name="deletePhotoSub">Delete this photo.</string>
    <string name="selectCar">Selected vehicle : </string>
    <string name="selectNoCar">Selected car : None</string>
    <string name="selectCategory">Please select a category.</string>
    <string name="stopWriting">Would you like to stop writing?</string>
    <string name="stopWritingSub">All content you write will be deleted.</string>
    <string name="makingList">Generating list ...</string>
    <string name="needPhoto">Please register your photo.</string>
    <string name="cannotAddPage">You can not add any more pages.</string>
    <string name="cannotDeletePage">You can not delete any more pages.</string>
    <string name="failedRegisterPost">Failed to register your post. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="failedModifyPost">Failed to modify your post. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="cmTab1">Popularity</string>
    <string name="cmTab2">Entirety</string>
    <string name="minutes"> minutes ago</string>
    <string name="hours"> hour ago</string>
    <string name="failedHandleImage">An error occurred while processing the image. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="canceled">It&apos;s been canceled.</string>
    <string name="boardAll">All</string>
    <string name="boardDaylife">Daylife</string>
    <string name="boardMarket">Sale</string>
    <string name="boardDiy">DIY</string>
    <string name="boardTest">Test</string>
    <string name="noticeTitle">Notice</string>
    <string name="tuning2Hint">Please enter brand or vehicle name.</string>
    <string name="communityHint">Please enter search terms.</string>
    <string name="deleteAccountCheck">You can not recover your account information after leaving the membership.\nAre you sure you want to leave the membership?</string>
    <string name="deleteAccountSub">Delete my account.</string>
    <string name="editNameTitle">Name (nickname)</string>
    <string name="editNameHint">Please enter a name or nickname.</string>
    <string name="editButton">Apply</string>
    <string name="strNoName">Name</string>
    <string name="strNoEmail">No Email</string>
    <string name="strNoAddress">No Address</string>
    <string name="strEventAlarm">Event Alarm</string>
    <string name="strEventAlarmExp">Events, Promotion-specific alarms</string>
    <string name="strOtherAlarm">Other Alarm</string>
    <string name="strOtherAlarmExp">Basic notifications including vehicle and part updates</string>
    <string name="strClause">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="strSuggest">Send Comments</string>
    <string name="strDeleteAccount">Delete My Account</string>
    <string name="strLogout">Log out</string>
    <string name="strPartner1">Company Type</string>
    <string name="strPartner2">Company Name</string>
    <string name="strPartner3">Contact or Email Address</string>
    <string name="strPartner4">Reasons for partnership request</string>
    <string name="strBoardAlllike">Like</string>
    <string name="strBoardAllcomment">Comment</string>
    <string name="strBoardNumberUnit"></string>
    <string name="strBoardDetailcomment">Please enter your comment.</string>

    <string name="strKakaoLoginStop">Stop Kakao Login: </string>
    <string name="strAddUserFail">An account with that email already exists. Please login with your original account.</string>
    <string name="strRequestEmailSent">We have sent you a verification email with the email you entered. Please check your mailbox.</string>
    <string name="strRequestEmailWait">E-mail authentication has not been completed. Please check your mailbox.</string>
    <string name="strRequestEmailCancel">The existing e-mail authentication has been cancelled because the user requested a different e-mail certificate. Please sign up as a new member.</string>
    <string name="strRequestEmailError">An error occurred during email authentication. Please try again. We are sorry for the inconvenience.</string>
    <string name="strEmailexisted1">The account registered with that email exists.(</string>
    <string name="strEmailexisted2">) Please login with your original account.</string>
    <string name="strEmailexisted3">) Please enter another email.</string>
    <string name="strSignoutErr">Error occurred during member withdrawal process. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="strSignoutSuccess">Membership withdrawal successful. Thank you for using.</string>
    <string name="strTooShortNickname">Nickname must be at least 4 characters.</string>
    <string name="strAddUserErr">Error occurred during member registration processing. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="strThereisNoEmail">Please enter your email.</string>
    <string name="strWarningData">"NOTICE\n\nThe 3D Car Modeling will be downloaded. A data calls will be incurred. We recommend you proceed in your WIFI environment. Once you have downloaded the modeling, you can use it without loading. (Except if there is an update.)\n\nAll images and contents are not available for commercial use, and the rights are reserved for our company. If you want to use it, please contact us. Personal use is permitted except for commercial use. Thank you."</string>

    <string name="versionLink">http://13.125.173.118:9000/version/version</string>
    <string name="check_User">http://13.125.173.118:9000/user/search_user</string>
    <string name="add_User">http://13.125.173.118:9000/user/add_user</string>
    <string name="update_User">http://13.125.173.118:9000/user/updt_user</string>
    <string name="delete_User">http://13.125.173.118:9000/user/remove_user</string>
    <string name="getCarLink">http://13.125.173.118:9000/car/get_car</string>
    <string name="carDBLink">http://13.125.173.118:9000/carSpec/list</string>
    <string name="traceLikeResult">http://13.125.173.118:9000/selectUserLikeBoardArticle</string>
    <string name="traceWritingResult">http://13.125.173.118:9000/selectUserBoardArticles</string>
    <string name="clause">https://m.cafe.naver.com/ArticleRead.nhn?clubid=29055312&amp;articleid=7&amp;page=1&amp;boardtype=L&amp;menuid=15</string>
    <string name="opinion">https://m.cafe.naver.com/SimpleArticleList.nhn?search.clubid=29055312&amp;search.menuid=23&amp;search.moreDirection=next</string>

    <string name="facebookGraphApi">"https://graph.facebook.com/"</string>

    <string name="http">http://</string>
    <string name="company">company</string>
    <string name="img_url">img_url</string>
    <string name="car_name">car_name</string>
    <string name="car_name_kor">car_name_kor</string>
    <string name="company_kor">company_kor</string>
    <string name="audi">AUDI</string>
    <string name="benz">BENZ</string>
    <string name="bmw">BMW</string>
    <string name="chevrolet">CHEVROLET</string>
    <string name="hyundai">HYUNDAI</string>
    <string name="kia">KIA</string>
    <string name="Volkswagen">VOLKSWAGEN</string>

    <string name="AccountTitle">How can I help you?</string>
    <string name="AccountSub">about Account,Convenience,etc.</string>
    <string name="AccountNoAddress">No Address</string>
    <string name="BasketTitle">Basket</string>
    <string name="BasketSub">Showing your purchase</string>
    <string name="HowtouseTitle">How to Use</string>
    <string name="HowtouseSub">See how apps are used</string>
    <string name="AllianceTitle">Alliance</string>
    <string name="AllianceSub">An alliance with Indicar</string>
    <string name="LogoutTitle">Logout</string>
    <string name="LogoutSub">Logout from the app</string>
    <string name="LikeTitle">Like</string>
    <string name="LikeSub">List of your favorite posts</string>
    <string name="MywritingTitle">My Writings</string>
    <string name="MywritingSub">List of your writings</string>
    <string name="MycommentTitle">My Comments</string>
    <string name="MycommentSub">List of your comments</string>

    <string name="term">Indicar Tuning  Standard Terms\n\n\nChapter 1 : The Purpose and Definition of the Standard Terms\n\nArticle 1 (The Purpose)\nThese Terms are intended to define the rights, obligations and responsibilities of the Company and its members in connection with the use of the apps and related services provided by Indicar Tuning.\n\nArticle 2 (Definition of Terms)\n① The definitions used in these Terms are as follows.\n1.”The company" means the provider of online app services.\n2. “The membership" means the person who agrees to these Terms and is authorized to use the App Service.\n3. “The user" means a member of the public who is subscribed to the App to use the App Service and to receive car tuning.\n4. “The business membership" means a member who is subscribed to an name of apprentice in order to receive a tuning quote from the app service to provide a tuning service, or means a member who subscribes in the name of a component company to register tuning parts with the app service and provide various parts to the user.\n5.”The App Service" means the basic services provided by the Company's apps and all accompanying services.\n6.”The 3D tuning service" refers to a service that shows real-time modeling of the tuning status of a car.\n7. "Account (ID)" means the combination of letters, numbers or special characters selected by the member and granted by the Company to identify the member and use the app service.\n8. "Account information" refers to the generic information provided by the member, such as the account of the member, password, and name, as well as generated information such as app usage information and log records.\n9. “The market" means a dutch auction service between users and tuning companies. When users publish a tuning quote that they want to receive, they can receive a quote from various companies and then they can select the quote you like and receive the tuning services.\n10. "Password" means a combination of letters, numbers, or special characters that the member himself or herself selects and keeps in a confidential manner in order to confirm that the member is a member that matches the account given to the member and to protect the information and rights of the member.\n11. "Construction example" means a board and service that promotes a tuning company by uploading the actual case of tuning construction performed in their company.\n12. "Community" means a board and its services that members freely talk to each other on tuning and other various topics (except for promotional purposes).\n13. "Post" means all information made up of characters, documents, pictures, sounds, images, or any combination thereof posted by a member in using the Service.\n ② The definitions of the terms used in these Terms and Conditions shall be governed by the relevant laws and ordinances and other common practices, except as provided in each item of Paragraph 1.\n\nArticle 3 (provision company information)\nThe company shall post the following information on the initial screen of the app service or on the app service homepage(http://cafe.naver.com/indicar) so that the members can easily understand the following information. However, the policy and terms of personal information handling can be viewed through the connection screen.\n1. The name of company and leader\n2. The email of company\n3. Phone number\n4.Corporate registration number\n5.Privacy Policy\n6. Services user’s agreement\n\nArticle 4 (Description and revision of the Terms and Conditions)\n① The company notifies the members of these terms by posting them on the initial screen of the app or on the app service website(http://cafe.naver.com/indicar) or by providing them with a link screen so that the members can know the contents of these terms.\n② The company shall take action so that the members can ask questions and respond to the contents of this Agreement with the company.\n③ The company must prepare the contents of the agreement so that those who wish to use the app service (hereinafter referred to as " users ") can easily understand the terms and conditions. And also, the company must provide important contents such as release or cancellation of contract, exemption of company and compensation for damages to the members.\n④ The company can revise these terms and conditions to the extent that they are not in violation of applicable laws.\n⑤ If the company revises the terms and conditions, the company notifies the application date, revision details, and reason of revision through the initial screen or the connection screen with the initial screen from at least seven days(30 days if the revision details is changes in the adverse or material to members) before the application date.\n⑥ In case the company modifies the terms and conditions, it shall check the member's consent on the application of the amended agreement after announcing the amendment agreement. In case the company notifies that we will be deemed to have agreed if the member does not express his or her consent or refusal about the revised terms and conditions, the company may be deemed to have agreed to the terms if the member does not show his or her intention to reject the agreement by the enforcement date.\n⑦ If the member does not agree to the application of the amendment terms, the company or the member may cancel the contract to use the app service.\n\nArticle 5 (Non-condition compliance)\nMatters not specified in this Terms and interpretation of these Terms shall be governed by the relevant laws.\nArticle 6 (Operational policy)\n① In order to protect the rights and interests of the members and to maintain order in the app service, the company shall set the scope of its policies(hereinafter referred to as “policies”) and operate the policies.\n② The company shall notify the members by posting the contents of the operation policy on the initial screen of the app or on the app service website or by providing the connection screen.\n③ In the case of an operation policy revision that has the same effect as bringing about a significant change to a member's rights or obligations or changing the terms and conditions, follow the procedure in Article 4. However, if the operation policy revision falls under any of the following clauses, it shall be notified in advance by the method described in paragraph 2.\n1. In case of revision of a matter of delegation by specifying the scope of the agreement\n2. In case of revision of matters unrelated to the rights and obligations of the member\n3. In case the contents of the operation policy are not fundamentally different from those set out in the Agreement and the member can accept the revision\n\n\nChapter 2 : The conclusion of a service contract\n\nArticle 6 (Application and method for use)\n① Those who want to use the app service provided by the company shall apply for the use of the membership function provided by the company in the initial screen of the app.\n② The users shall provide all information required by the company when applying for use.\n③ The users shall record their actual information when applying for use in paragraph 1. The member can not claim the rights of a member under this Agreement if his or her real name or identifying information are false or stolen. Also, in this case, the company may cancel or terminate the contract without a refund.\n\nArticle 7 (Accept and restrict the application)\n① The company accepts the application for use if the user applies for the actual information the company requires, except there is no reason for refusing the application.\n② The company may refuse to accept any of the following applications.\n1. In case of an application for use in violation of Article 7\n2. In case of application by a retired user within the last 3 months\n3. In case the company needs to limit its services to specific countries\n4. In case of a user application for an offence prohibited by the relevant statutes\n5. In case the consent is deemed inappropriate for other reasons falling under paragraphs 1 to 4\n③ The company may suspend its acceptance until any of the following reasons are resolved.\n1. In case the company has insufficient facilities or technical difficulties\n2. In case of service failure\n3. In case it is difficult to accept the application for the reasons listed above\n\nArticle 8 (Member account (ID) and password)\n① The company assigns the account a certain number, number, or combination of special characters selected by the members for the convenience of protecting the members ' information and informing them of service use.\n② The company carries out all member management activities, including availability of services by the respective members through account information.\n③ The members shall manage their account information in accordance with their duties as a good administrator. The member shall be responsible for damages caused by the member's neglect of his account information or consent to a third party.\n④ The members are responsible for the management of their password and can change the password at any time for security reasons.\n⑤ The member shall change his password regularly.\n\nArticle 9(Provision and modification of member information)\n① The members shall provide the company with the factual information in the case that it is required to provide information under these terms and conditions. If disadvantages occur due to false information provided by the member, the member shall not be protected.\n② The members can access and edit their personal information at any time through the Personal Information Management screen. However, the account (ID) required for service management can not be modified.\n③ The member shall modify the details of application for membership or notify the change to the company by other means when their information has changed.\n④ The company shall not be held liable for any disadvantages caused by failure to notify the company of any changes in paragraph 2.\n\nArticle 10 (Protection and management of personal information)\n① The company shall strive to protect the members' personal information, including account information, as provided under the pertinent statutes. The related statutes and the company's policy of handling personal information shall apply to the protection and use of members' personal information.\n② The company's privacy policy does not apply to services provided by third parties that are simply linked to the website and game services website.\n③ The company shall not be held liable for any information, including the member's account information, that has been disclosed due to reasons attributable to the member.\n\n\nChapter 3 : The obligations of the contracting parties\n\nArticle 11 (The obligations of the company)\n① The company complies with the relevant statutes, and the company shall faithfully carry out its rights and obligations under these terms and conditions.\n② The company shall establish a security system to protect the personal information (including credit information) so that the members can use the service safely, and the company publishes and complies with the privacy policy. The company shall prevent the members ' personal information from being disclosed or provided to third parties except as provided under these terms and the Privacy Policy.\n③ The company can fail in its facilities or lost data when the company updates its service in order to ensure continued and stable service provision. In this case, the company makes every effort to repair any abnormalities without delay, unless there is an inevitable reason, such as a natural disaster, an emergency, or a defect or a disability that can not be solved by current technology.\n\nArticle 12 (A duty of membership)\n① The member shall not doing these deeds.\n1. Writing false details when applying or changing\n2. Stealing information from others\n3. An act to impersonate executives, employees, operators and other persons in a company\n4. Changing in information posted by the company\n5. Sending or posting prohibited information (such as computer programs)\n6. The act of producing, distributing, using or advertising computer programs or devices not provided or approved by the company\n7. Infringement of intellectual property rights, including copyright of the company and other third parties\n8. An act that undermines the reputation of the company and other third parties, or disturbs the company and other third parties\n9. An act to disclose or post information that is contrary to the meaning of obscene or violent language, text, video, sound, or other public statements\n10. An act to use app services for profit, sales, advertising and political activities without the consent of the company\n11. Other prohibited by relevant laws or not permitted by good manners or other social customs\n② The members shall check and comply with the provisions of these terms and conditions, cautions and notices notified by the company regarding the use and app services.\n③ The company may define the specific types of acts in its operation policy falling under Article 1 or Article 2 or following paragraphs. The members are obliged to comply them.\n1. Restrictions on member's account name\n2. Restrictions on the use of app services\n3. Restrictions on using boards\n4. Other items recognized as necessary for the company to operate the app services without prejudice to the members' essential rights to use the app services\n\n\nChapter 4 : Service use\n\nArticle 13 (Changes and modifications to the service)\n① The members can use the app services in accordance with these terms and conditions, operation policies, and game rules set by the company.\n② The app services provided by the company are created by the company, so the company has comprehensive authority on the production, modification, maintenance, and maintenance of the service.\n③ The company takes necessary steps to protect app services from a variety of risks and to maintain order in the community.\n④ The company can update the app service on a regular basis. In this case, the app service and app service website are notified after a change.\n\nArticle 14 (Provision and suspension of services, etc.)\n① App services are provided 24 hours a day according to the company's sales policy. The company will guide the delivery of the app service in an appropriate way to the app's initial screen or the app service homepage (http://cafe.naver.com/indicar).\n② Notwithstanding paragraph 1, app service may not be available for a certain period of time if one of the following occurs. During that time, the company is not required to provide app services.\n1. Maintenance inspection, replacement, and regular inspection of information and communication facilities such as computers\n2. Necessity to address electronic breaches such as hacking, communications accidents, members' unusual app usage, or unpredicted instability in app services\n3. In case the related statutes prohibit the provision of app services at a specific time or method\n4. In case it is impossible to provide normal app service because of natural disasters, emergencies, power outages, failures of service facilities, congestion of service use, or other reason\n5. In case the need of the management of the company like dividing, merging, transfer, closing operations, lower profits from other app services\n③ In the case of paragraph 2. 1, the company may suspend the game service at intervals of two weeks or a month. In this case, the company will notify the members of this information at least 24 hours in advance of the app's initial screen or on the app service website (http://cafe.naver.com/indicar).\n④ In case of paragraph 2.2, the company can temporarily suspend the app service without notice. In such cases, the company may report this on the initial screen of the game or on the Game Service homepage later (http://cafe.naver.com/indicar).\n⑤ The company shall not be liable for any damages to the users in connection with the use of the company's free service. However, damages caused by intentional or serious negligence of the company shall be excluded.\n⑥ In the case of paragraphs 2.3 or 2.5, the company can suspend all app services due to technical and operational requirements. In this case, the company may notify the website 30 days in advance and stop providing app services. In the event of unavoidable circumstances that can not be notified in advance, the notification may be made after the suspending.\n⑦ If the company terminates the app service according to paragraph 7, the member can not claim damages for the free service or paid service that has been completed.\n\nArticle 15 (The provision of information)\nThe company displays the following on the initial screen of the app or on its Internet website, the App Service homepage (http://cafe.naver.com/indicar) for members.\n1. Company name\n2. App Name\n3.Utilization grade\n4.Classification number\n5.Date of production\n6. Distributor's report number or registration number\n7. Other matters recognized by the company as necessary\n\nArticle 16 (Collection of information, etc.)\n① The company can store all postings between members within the app service. The company shall access this information only when it is deemed necessary for the members to adjust disputes, handle complaints, or maintain order of app services. Also, this information is reserved by the company and must not be accessed by any third party not authorized by law. However, the reason for the user's subsequent access to the chat information and the information related to him shall be notified in case the member's posting information needs to be accessed about account theft, cash transactions, verbal abuse, fraud in the game, bug abuse, and other current violations, and investigation, treatment, verification and relief of any serious breach of the Agreement as provided under Article 13 of this Agreement. \n② To improve the quality of app services, such as operation of app services and stabilization of applications, the company can collect and utilize the members ' mobile phone settings and specifications information. The member can deny access to the device through additional permission settings.\n\nArticle 17 (Utilization)\n① The company may provide game services for the members to use at no extra charge (hereinafter called " free service ") and services to broker transactions between users and business members (' market ‘), and Members can select an app service to use.\n② Payment by market is not made through app service. App services only do broker transactions between users and business members, and each member shall handle further transactions or other inquiries.\n③ In connection with the use of the market in paragraph 1, the member shall comply with the following matters when using the market.\n1. All members who use the market should not enter false information. If the member enter false information, the member may be punished according to the terms and conditions, and if the degree is severe, he or she may be punished by civil or criminal.\n2. Users who make transactions through the market must pay the payment to the company member within the designated time and the company member shall provide the service to the member within the designated time. If a member violates these matters, he or she may also be punished according to the terms and conditions and civil and criminal penalties.\n3. Members who often cancel transactions in the market may be restricted or prohibited from using the market.\n\nArticle 18 (The imputation of copyright, etc.)\n① Copyright and other intellectual property rights to the contents produced by the company in the app service belong to the company.\n② The members cannot use the information obtained by using the app service provided by the company to replicate, transmit, publish, distribute or broadcast for commercial purposes without prior approval of the company.\n③ The members shall allow the company to use all data and information like communication, image and sound that are included posts that are viewed within the app or uploaded or transmitted by members or other users in connection with the app service (hereinafter called " user content ") in the following ways and conditions.\n1. Using the user's content, changing the editing format and other modifications (It is available in any form and has no restrictions on the duration and location of use. "Any form" includes publication, reproduction, performance, transmission, distribution, broadcasting and creation of secondary work.)\n2. Do not sell, rent or transfer user content for the purpose of transaction without prior consent from the user who created the user content.\n④ The company shall not commercially use the contents(for example, postings to general boards) of the members who are not shown within the app and are not integrated with the game service without the explicit consent of the members. Also, the member may delete these user contents at any time.\n⑤ If the company determines that the postings and contents in the app service to be posted or registered by the member are subject to the prohibited acts prescribed in Article 13, the company can delete them or reject them without prior notice.\n⑥ A member whose legal profits are violated due to information posted on the bulletin board operated by the company may request the company to delete the information or publish a statement. In this case, the company promptly takes the necessary actions and notifies the applicant.\n⑦ Paragraph 3 is valid while the company operates the app service and applies continuously even after withdrawal from the membership.\n\n\nChapter 5 : Discontinuation, termination and usage restrictions\n\nArticle 19 (The cancellation of a member)\n① The member may cancel the contract for using the app service (hereinafter referred to as withdrawal). If a member requests withdrawal from the membership, the company can check the member's identity and take actions according to the member's application if the member is identified as himself.\n② If a member wishes to withdraw from the membership, he or she can withdraw from the membership through the process of withdrawal from the customer center and service.\n\nArticle 20 (The termination of a company)\n① The company may terminate the contract after notifying the members in advance in the event that the members violate their obligations under this Agreement. However, in the event a member damages the company by violating the current law, intentional or serious negligence, the service contract may be terminated without prior notice.\n② When the company cancels the service contract, the company notifies the member of the following matters in writing, e-mail, or in a similar way. \n1.Reasons for cancellation\n2.Termination Date\n③ In the case of a lead in paragraph 1, the member shall lose the right to use all services and shall not claim a refund or damages.\n\nArticle 21 (Restrict service use to members)\n① The company may restrict the members from using the app service according to the following classification. The reasons for the specific violation of the membership's obligations shall be decided in the operation policy of the app service pursuant to Article 27.\n1. Community Usage Restriction : Restrict members ' access to the community for a period of time or permanently\n2. Account usage restrictions : Restrict the use of member accounts for a certain period or permanently\n3. Restriction of membership : Restrict members to use app services for a certain period or permanently\n② In case the company's usage limit is justified, the company shall not compensate the member for damages caused by the restriction.\n\nArticle 22 (Restrictions of usage as temporary measures)\n① The company may suspend the account until the investigation is complete on any of the following issues.\n1. A legitimate report that the account was hacked or stolen\n2. In case of reasonable suspicion as an offender, such as the user of an illegal program\n3. In case temporary action of the account is required for reasons falling under the foregoing.\n② In the case of paragraph 1, the company will release the suspension of the account after the investigation is completed. However, if it is found to be an offence under paragraph 1, the suspension cannot be released.\n\nArticle 23 (Reason and procedure for restriction of usage)\n① The company defines the specific reasons and procedures for which the usage limit is implemented in consideration of the details, degree, frequency, and outcome of the violation.\n② In the event of a company's restriction of use as specified in Article 25, the following items shall be notified to the members in writing or by posting them on the electronic mail, the initial screen of the game, or on the app service website (http://cafe.naver.com/indicar). \n1. Reasons for restriction\n2. Type and duration of usage restrictions\n3. Objection application method against usage restrictions\n\nArticle 24 (Procedure for objection to usage restrictions)\n① When a member intends to oppose the company's usage restriction, the member shall submit an application for his or her objection to the company's usage restriction in writing, e-mail, or in a corresponding manner within 15 days from the date of notification.\n② The company that receives the objection application under paragraph 1 shall answer the member's objection in writing, e-mail or equivalent within 15 days of receiving the application. However, the company shall notify the member of the reason and the schedule for handling the problem if it is not able to respond within 15 days.\n③ The company must take appropriate action in accordance with the above responses.\n\n\nChapter 6 : Compensation and refund, etc.\n\nArticle 25 (Compensation for damages)\n① In the event the company intentionally or involuntarily damages the member, the company is liable for damages.\n② In the event a member does damage to the company in violation of these terms and conditions, the member shall be liable for damages to the company.\n\nArticle 26 (Company immunity)\n① The company shall be exempted from liability if it can not provide services for war, accident, natural disasters, emergency situations, technical defects that can not be solved by current technology, or for unavoidable reasons.\n② The company is exempted from liability for suspension of game services, failure to use the service, and termination of contract due to reasons attributable to the members.\n③ The company shall be exempted from liability if damages occur to members by the primary communication service provider suspending or not providing telecommunication services normally.\n④ In case the app service is stopped or disabled due to inevitable reasons such as repair, replacement, regular inspection, or construction of the equipment for the app service, no liability of the company is granted unless it is intentional or serious negligence of the company.\n⑤ The company shall be exempted from any problems caused by the members ' smart phone environment or by the network environment without any intentional or serious negligence of the company.\n⑥ The company shall not be held liable for information, data, reliability of facts, or accuracy posted or transmitted by members or third parties in the app service or website unless the company is intentional or grave negligence.\n⑦ The company has no obligation to intervene in disputes between the members or between the members and third parties in which an app service has been used as a medium, nor is it liable to compensate for damages. \n⑧ The Company only serves as a broker of transactions between you and the members of the Company in the Market, but does not doing tuning directly. Therefore, if any of the transactions between you and a business member are damaged, the liability of the company will be exempted unless the company intervened in the transaction beyond the role of a broker.\n⑨ In the event a member of the company places a false or exaggerated advertisement in the construction case, and the user is damaged, the company will not be responsible for the construction case unless it is poorly managed or otherwise interpreated.\n⑩ Some app services in this app service may be provided through app services provided by other service operators. Also, the company shall be exempted from liability for damages caused by app services provided by other service providers unless the company is intentionally or significantly negligent.\n⑪ The company shall not be liable for damages caused by a member's smartphone error, or for any damages caused by incorrect description or omission of personal information or e-mail address.\n⑫ The company can limit app service hours according to relevant laws and government policies or members. So, The company shall be exempted from all responsibilities related to the use of app services arising out of such restrictions and restrictions.\n\nArticle 27 (Handling members' grievances and resolving disputes)\n① The company provides information that how to present the members' opinions or complaints on the app guide screen or on the app service website for their convenience.The company operates a dedicated organization to handle these members' opinions or complaints.\n② The company shall promptly handle any comments or complaints raised by the members within a reasonable period if they are objectively recognized as legitimate. However, in case of an extended period of processing, the members are notified to the app service website (http://cafe.naver.com/indicar) about the reason and the processing schedule, or are notified by e-mail, phone, or written.\n③ If a third party dispute control agency adjusts a dispute between the company and the member, the company can faithfully demonstrate the matters controlled by the member, such as usage restrictions, and follow the mediation of the adjustment agency.\n\nArticle 28 (Notice to Members)\n① If the company notifies the members, the e-mail address or electronic memo designated by the member can be used.\n② The company may substitute with the notification under paragraph 1 by posting the notification on the initial screen of the company's app site or presenting a pop-up screen for 7 days or more if the entire member is notified.\n\nArticle 29 (Jurisdiction and governing laws)\nThese terms and conditions are regulated and interpreted according to the laws of each country, and in the event of a lawsuit arising from disputes between the company and its members, a court of jurisdiction shall be governed by the procedures set forth in the Act.\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nPrivacy Policy\n\nIn accordance with the Privacy Act, the company implements the following measures to protect the users ' privacy and interests and to handle the personal information problems smoothly. The company will notify through a notice of the website(or individual notice) if the policy for personal information processing is revised.\n\n○ This policy will take effect on 16 July 2017.\n\n\n1. Purpose of personal information processing\nThe company processes the personal information for the following purposes. The personal information processed will not be used for any purpose other than the following and will seek prior consent if the purpose of use is changed.\n\nA. Sign up and management homepage membership\n\nThe company processes the personal information for the following purposes : Confirmation of membership intent, maintenance and management of membership status, enforcement of limited identification system, prevention of service fraud, notification and complaints.\n\n\nB. Delivery of goods or services\n\nThe company processes the personal information for the following purposes : Service delivery, content delivery, custom service delivery, authentication, etc.\n\n\nC. Use for marketing and advertising\n\nThe company processes the personal information for the following purposes : Developing new services (products) and providing customized services, providing event and advertising information and providing opportunities for participation, identifying access frequency or statistics on member service use, etc. \n\n\n\n\n2. Privacy file status\n\nA. The file name of personal information : Member.db\n- Privacy Topics : Email, mobile phone number, password, login ID, service use history, connection log\n- Collection Method : Collection via the creation information gathering tool, Android app, iOS app\n- A holding ground : The company collects and maintains personal information for each member to store personal information, and to provide broker services and other customized services.\n- Retention period : Semi-permanent(However, when a member leaves the membership, the member is deleted with a grace period of one month.)\n- Relevant laws : Following the relevant laws of each country\n\n\n\n\n3. The processing and retention period of personal information\n\n① The company shall keep and maintain personal information within the period of personal information retention and utilization pursuant to the statutes or personal information that has been agreed upon when collecting personal information from an information subject.\n\n② Each personal information processing and retention period is as follows.\n\n1.(Providing goods or services)\nThe personal information related to (Providing goods or services) shall be retained and used for the purposes of the above use, from the date of consent for collection and utilization (1 year).\n- A holding ground : Required to provide services for each user to decorate their own tuned vehicle and connect it to the labour force provider\n- Relevant laws : 1)Records on the handling of consumer complaints or disputes : 3 years\n2) Records on markings and advertising : 6 months\n\n\n\n4. Matters concerning the providing personal information for third party\n\n① The company provides personal information to third parties only when it is subject to the Privacy Act, such as the consent of the information body and special regulations of the law.\n\n② The company provides personal information to third parties as follows.\n\n\na)\n- Company who receives personal information : Indicar Tuning\n- Category of personal information use by the recipient : Email, mobile phone number, password, login ID\n- Period of use by the recipient : Semi-permanent (However, when a member leaves the membership, the member is deleted with a grace period of one month.)\n\n\n\n\n\n5. The body of personal information may exercise the following rights as a personal information entity. \n\n① The informatory may exercise the following rights to the Company at any time. \n1. Requiring access to personal information\n2. Requiring correction if there is an error\n3.Requiring Delete\n4. Requiring stop processing\n② Rights under section 1 may be exercised in writing, e-mail, and in copy transmission (FAX) pursuant to the Privacy Act. The company will take this action without delay.\n③ In case the information subject requests correction or deletion of personal information errors, the company shall not use or provide such personal information until the correction or deletion is completed.\n④ The exercise of rights pursuant to paragraph 1 shall be carried out through the legal representative of the information body or by the authorized party. In this case, you must submit a letter of attorney under the Privacy Act.\n\n\n\n6. Items of personal information being processed\n\n① The company handles the following personal information items. \n- Required items : email, mobile phone number, password, login ID\n- Optional : None\n\n\n\n\n7. The destruction of personal information shall in principle destroy the personal information without delay if the purpose of personal information processing is achieved. The procedure, expiration date, and method of destruction are as follows.\n\n- The information entered by the user shall be transferred to a separate DB upon achievement of the purpose (separate documents on paper) and stored for a period of time or immediately destroyed according to the internal policy and other related statutes. At this time, personal information transferred to DB is not used for any purpose other than by law.\n- The member’s personal information shall be destroyed within five days from the end of the period when the retention period of the member’s personal information has expired. If personal information is not required, such as the purpose of personal information fulfillment, the abolition of the service, and the termination of the business, the personal information shall be destroyed within five days from the date when the personal information processing is deemed unnecessary.\n\n- 파기방법\nElectronic file type information uses a technical method in which the recording can not be played back.\n\n\n\n8. Measures to secure the safety of personal information\nUnder the Privacy Act, the company takes the following technical and administrative and physical actions necessary for securing safety.\n\n1. Regular self-auditing\nTo ensure stability in relation to personal information handling, the company conduct our own audit regularly (once a quarter).\n\n2. Establishing and implementing an internal management plan\nInternal management plans are established and implemented for the safe handling of personal information.\n\n3. Encryption of personal information\nThe user's personal information and password are encrypted and stored and managed, so only the user can know them. Also, Critical data uses separate security features, such as encrypting files, transfer data and using file locking.\n\n4. Access restriction to personal information\nWe are taking necessary measures to control access to personal information through the granting, modification and cancellation of access to the data processing system. Also, The intrusion prevention system controls unauthorized access from outside.\n\n\n\n\n9. A person who protects his personal information\n\n\n① To be responsible for personal information processing, to handle complaints and to relieve damages by the information body, the company assigns a personal information protection agent as follows.\n\n▶ A person who protects his personal information\nName : Su Mong-Woo\nOfficial responsibilities : Development Team Leader\nPosition : Development Team Leader\nContact information : incar_candykick@naver.com\n※ ▶ Department for Personal Information Protection\nName of department : Development Team\nThe person in charge : Su Mong-Woo\nContact information : incar_candykick@naver.com\n② You can inquire the owner and responsible department about all inquiries, complaints, and damages caused by using the company's services (or business) related privacy. The company will answer and process inquiries from the information body without delay.\n\n\n\n11. Changing privacy policy\n\n① This Privacy Policy shall be applied from the date of enforcement. In the event of any changes made in accordance with the statutes and policies, it shall be notified through notice from the 7th day before the implementation of the change.</string>
    <string name="server_not_available">http request failure 서버 응답없음 ---------------</string>
    <string name="data_not_available">response data not available 데이터 처리 오류 ---------------</string>
    <string name="photo_from_storage_not_available">photo from storage not available 저장소에서 사진 불러오기 오류 ---------------</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tutorial">Tutorial</string>
    <string name="filter_board_type_label">&lt; Post Type &gt;</string>
    <string name="filter_car_type_label">&lt; Vehicle Type &gt;</string>
    <string name="search_box_hint">Please enter a search term.</string>
    <string name="Splash_wait">Please Wait</string>
</resources>